watchserieshd.eu 2011-09-20

# Watch Tv Series HD - Online Series, Episodes

**SearchSeries Privacy Policy**  
Thank you for visiting the WatchSeriesHD website. This privacy policy governs your use of www.Search-Series.com and any other sites operated by Search-Series.com that bear this privacy policy ("Websites"). We regard your privacy seriously and provide this Privacy Policy to describe which information we collect, how we collect it, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may share it. 

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**  
You may use the Websites without registering. You may also register and voluntarily provide personally identifiable information ("PII"), such as your name and email address. When you create your account, we will ask you to create a username and password. You will be able to enter PII into your password-protected account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and your account information. In addition, WatchSeriesHD allows you to set up profiles that may be viewed by users of the Websites. To enrich your experience, you may choose to include some PII in your public profile so that other users can identify you. You can change or delete your profile at anytime. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We may collect non-personally identifiable information ("Non-PII") such as your internet protocol address and information associated with your computer, browser and network to deliver services or information, provide notices, track usage, verify your authority to use the Websites, store your preferences, and generally improve the content and functionality of the Websites 

**Cookies**  
We may use small text files stored in your browser called cookies to store your preferences, record session information, and improve your experience on the Websites as described in the previous sentence. WE DO NOT ASSOCIATE COOKIES WITH THE PII YOU SUBMIT IN YOUR ACCOUNT. 

**Advertising**  
We will not share your PII with advertising companies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. Such advertising companies may set cookies and collect session information, such as your IP address, to target advertisements to you based on your internet protocol address, and information associated with your computer, browser or network. You may be able to configure your browser to reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Many of our advertising partners are part of the Network Advertising Initiative. You may opt-out of behavioral advertising for Network Advertising Initiative member companies by following the link below and opting-out of all or some of the advertising networks: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Disclosure**  
We will not intentionally disclose PII in your account except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy. Non-PII may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements. We may also disclose your PII and Non-PII if we believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, or to prevent harm to yourself or others. In addition, we may transfer your PII to a successor entity upon a change of control of Search-Series.com, sale, merger, or other corporate reorganization. Such successor entity will be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**Email**  
Email addresses are used for identification, inviting new friends to WatchSeriesHD, searching for and finding friends, for general communication, and to send notifications to you. To facilitate searching for and finding friends on the Websites, WatchSeriesHD allows users to search for other members using text searches, first and last name, email address, and other attributes. Users can invite friends to join WatchSeriesHD by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. WatchSeriesHD stores these email addresses so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to establish relationships between users. WatchSeriesHD does not sell invitation email addresses or use them for any other purpose. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
The Websites contain links to other websites. Your use of websites to which the Websites link is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on such third party websites. 

**Security**  
WatchSeriesHD employs procedural and technological measures, such as password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to protect your information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

**Policy Changes**  
WatchSeriesHD reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and will post any revisions on the Websites. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Websites will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last revised April 14, 2011. 

If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please [_contact us_](http://watchserieshd.eu/info/contact).
